hapihhost.in 2019-11-08

# Privacy Policy | Hapih Host

### **Privacy Policy**

 **Hapihhost.in**  respects your individual privacy. This Privacy Policy (‘Policy’) embodies our commitment to its protection through adherence to fair electronic information practices. This Policy puts you, the individual, in control of how your personal information is processed. You have our promise that we will not electronically process your personal information in any way that is incompatible with this Policy and will not share any of your information unless we receive written permission from you.

This Privacy Policy protects your privacy by

 **Informing you about:**

The types of personal information Hapihhost.in collects about you through its Website;

How it collects that information;

The general purposes for which it collects such information;

The types of organizations to which it discloses the information;

The choices and means by which individuals may limit its use and disclosure.

 **Empowering you to choose:**

Whether and how certain personal information you provide is used (where such use is unrelated to the uses for which you originally disclosed it); and Whether and the manner in which a third party uses certain personal information you provide (where such use is unrelated to the uses for which you originally disclosed it).

 **Assuring you that Hapihhost.in:**

Takes reasonable precautions to protect personal information from loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration or destruction;

Implements reasonable policies and procedures to ensure that personal information is kept only for the purposes for which it has been gathered;

Uses reasonable measures to ensure that we have accurately and completely recorded the personal information you have provided; and

Provides you reasonable access to your personal information as well as procedures for correcting or modifying that information where appropriate

 **Getting to Know Our Customers**

We are the Internet’s leading domain name registrar and web hosting company because we have taken the time to get acquainted with our customers. We get to know you primarily through the information you provide to us when signing up for, or using, one or more of our services. The information you provide ranges from basic contact information, to payment information, to the technical coordinates of your host servers. The application for web hosting registration found at www.Hapihhost.in is a representative illustration of the information we request of you. All of the information we request from you when purchasing our services is obligatory unless otherwise noted on the relevant form. When you purchase our services, you agree to provide and maintain accurate, complete and updated information including your name, email, address and phone. After you have signed up for our services, we may be in communication with you about your account, technical questions you may have about services provided by us, or any other matter relating to those services. Those communications are essential to our relationship with you and to our ability to provide you with quality services that are responsive to your needs. At the same time, those communications give us helpful insights about you, your preferences and the ways in which we might improve our services. We therefore may maintain this information for future use. For operational and quality assurance purposes, we take note of whether and how you use the information and services that we provide, such as by recording site traffic patterns and by maintaining log files of users’ access to site files.

The information we receive from or about you is stored on systems designed to prevent the loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration or destruction of that information. The sensitive information, in terms of Information technology Act, 2000, collected at Hapihhost.in includes credit card numbers and account passwords. The account password is used by a Customer to gaining access to the services and is not used or accessed by HostngRaja.in or its affiliates / partners in any way, whereas the Credit Card details are processed at the Payment Gateway end, who are PCI Compliant and do not retain the sensitive information for the period more than required. The transmission of said sensitive information is encrypted in the interest of heightened privacy protection and information integrity.

Further, transactions within our account manager and purchase flows use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) encryption when transmitting data from your connection to our systems. You may click the lock icon within your web browser to verify the authenticity of any or our SSL certificates.

 **Information Corrections or Changes**

You have the ability to correct or change certain information in our records, such as your address and contact information. The process for changing your information begins at https://www.Hapihhost.in/login and then click on the My Details menu. You may change this information at any time and as often as necessary. If you need assistance or have questions about correcting information, you can contact us via e-mail at support@Hapihhost.in

 **How We Put Information to Good Use**

We use information about you for purposes of monitoring and improving our internal operations, as well as to ensure we: (i) bill you properly, (ii) administer your account in accordance with your agreements with us, and (iii) properly perform the services you have requested.

We also use the information we collect to monitor and improve our internal operations, as well as to improve the experience of users in our network of sites. For example, we may correlate Website traffic information with data about individual users. This data helps us to determine how much our customers use parts of the site, allowing us to enhance it to fit the needs of as many of our customers as possible. We may also break down overall usage statistics according to customers’ domain names, browser types, and MIME types by reading this information from the browser string (information contained in every user’s browser).

Another example of our use of information to enhance the experience of users in our network of sites is our reliance on cookie files. We use cookie files to make it easier for users to access our site or services. A cookie file is a small data file that certain Websites write to your hard drive when you visit them. A cookie file can contain information such as a user ID that the site uses to track the pages you have visited. However, the only personal information a cookie can contain is information you supply yourself. A cookie cannot read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other sites. We use cookies to track user traffic patterns (as described above) when you register for Hapihhost.in services. When you register, we may use a cookie to store a unique, random user ID. We use this ID to identify you anonymously in our database and to track the pages you visit on our site.

If you have set your browser to warn you before accepting cookies, you will receive the warning message with each cookie. You may refuse cookies by turning them off in your browser; however, some of our web pages may require a cookie for access.

Further, we use the information we collect to direct important notices and information affecting your account or services, as well as to provide general information that may be of interest to you, including newsletters, surveys, contest and sweepstake announcements, and information about our service or product offerings or the offerings of our business affiliates. You may opt-out of receiving information from us simply by notifying us of your desire in accordance with the opt-out instructions contained in any information message you receive from us. Note, however, that in order to fulfill our service obligations to you, we must continue sending you notices and other important information affecting your account or services.

Finally, Hapihhost.in holding sensitive/ personal data or information of providers of information, shall not retain such information for longer than is required for the purposes for which the information may lawfully be used or is otherwise required under the User Agreement or any other law for the time being in force or unless ordered to the contrary by any order of court of law. The information collected shall be used for the purpose for which it has been collected. The information is collected and retained by Hapihhost.in on it’s server located at various locations in India.

 **With Whom We May Share Information**

Pursuant to arrangements with Internet Corporation for Assigned Names and Numbers (‘ICANN’), we compile and maintain a publicly accessible registration database that includes basic information about each domain name registered with us, including the names, telephone numbers and e-mail addresses of individuals designated as points of contact for a given domain name. Whether or not applicable domain name registration fees have been paid is also publicly accessible. With the gradual continued privatization of the Domain Name System, and consistent with the rules or policies applicable to that system, or to comply with any changes in law or regulation, we may, if appropriate, take steps to restrict the accessibility and amount of personally identifying information available in the registration database

When you register a domain name through us, we must disclose your domain name and its associated Internet Protocol (“IP”) numbers to the appropriate registry in order to make your chosen domain name a functional address on the Internet. Certain registries also require that we disclose to them the names, postal addresses, telephone and fax numbers, and e-mail addresses of individuals designated as the registrant or points of contact for a given domain name. Each registry discloses certain portions (and in some cases all) of the information we are required to provide to them about your domain name registration. For example, each registry discloses at least each registered domain name and its associated IP numbers (“TLD zone files”) to TLD server administrators so that the domain name is capable of functioning as an address on the Internet. Consistent with the current rules and policies for the Domain Name System, such registries also disclose the TLD zone files to other interested persons, provided those persons agree, among other things, not to use the TLD zone files for improper purposes, including the transmission of unsolicited commercial e-mail. Similarly, each registry may compile and maintain a publicly accessible database that includes basic information about each domain name registered with that registry, including the names, telephone and fax numbers, and e-mail addresses of individuals designated as the registrant or points of contact for a given domain name.

We may share certain information about you with those of our vendors who are responsible for handling your account or performing other services that you require but no sensitive information is shared by any third party vendors. But we will not share such information with other third parties, except in response to formal requests (e.g., subpoena or court order) made in connection with litigation, arbitration, or criminal proceedings directly relating to a domain name registration or other services we provide, or as directed by you or your agent. Additionally, we may share the information stored on the publicly accessible registration database, as well as other information that is not of a sensitive nature, with carefully selected business partners, including those who offer services that complement those provided by us or which may otherwise be of interest to you. Please note, however, that consistent with the current rules and policies for the Domain Name System, information about you must remain available in the publicly accessible registration database.

 **Our Accountability to You**

By purchasing our services, you obtain the protections of, and consent to the data processing practices described in, this Privacy Policy. When you purchase our services, you also represent to us that you have provided notice to, and obtained consent from, any third party individuals whose personal data you supply to us with regard to: (i) the purposes for which such third party’s personal data have been collected, (ii) the intended recipients or categories of recipients of the third party’s personal data, (iii) which of the third party’s data are obligatory and which data, if any, are voluntary, and (iv) how the third party can access and, if necessary, rectify the data held about them.

In addition to the privacy protections that we provide, our employees, agents and business partners are independently responsible for ensuring compliance with this Privacy Policy, as described below.

 **Employee Accountability**

Only those Hapihhost.in employees that have a legitimate business purpose for accessing and handling personal information obtained by us are given authorization to do so. The unauthorized access or use of such information by a Hapihhost.in employee is prohibited and constitutes grounds for disciplinary action. Additionally, our information management systems are configured in such a way as to block or inhibit employees from accessing information that they have no authority to access.

The Accountability of Hapihhost.in’s Agents and Business Partners

Our trusted vendors and business partners are responsible for processing or handling some of the information that we receive. These vendors and business partners are not authorized to use such information for purposes beyond those specified by us and are required to preserve the confidentiality with which we treat such information.

If you feel that Hapihhost.in, or any of our agents, representatives or employees, is violating this Privacy Policy, please contact us via e-mail at info@Hapihhost.in

 **Notification of Changes**

We will post any changes to this Privacy Policy 30 days before their effective date so you will always know what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. You are responsible for periodically checking our Website for changes to this Privacy Policy.

###  **Jurisdiction**

  * The jurisdiction of all matters would be at Jaipur, Rajasthan, in case of any dispute.
